

PROFILE

A highly focused software developer with experience in a variety of development and engineering positions. Organized, methodical and a keen eye for detail results in solid coding and trustworthy software programs. Understanding client requirements and communicating the progress of projects are core values in achieving long lasting business relationships.

CONTACT

PHONE:

+91-7985380783, +91-7753992339

EXPERTISE

C#, Dot Net Core, Angular, Asp. Net

Mvc,WebForms,SQL Server,

Python, Django, HTML, CSS, JS, Query,

Bootstrap.

EMAIL:

joshi.programmer@gmail.com

LINKEDIN:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/joshi00

HOBBIES

Music.

Sports and Exercise.

KAILASH CHANDRA JOSHI

<Full Stack Web Developer/>

EDUCATION

MASTERS IN COMPUTER APPLICATION

Sep 2013-Sep 2015

GPA: 80%

Bachelor in Computer Application

Mar 2009 - Sep 2011

GPA: 77%

Intermediate (UP Board)

Year 2007 GPA: 66%

High School (UP Board)

Year 2005 GPA: 62%

WORK EXPERIENCE

Cetpa Infotech Pvt. Ltd. Noida [Dot Net Developer]

Oct 2019- Present

URL : https://www.cetpainfotech.com/

URL: https://studentquery.cetpainfotech.com/login.aspx

- Design, development and Maintenance of WebApplication using Asp. Net, SQL Server.
- Applied ADO. Net to pull data out of the database and use it in the application.

Vedang Hospitality Pvt. Ltd. New Delhi [Dot Net Developer]

Sep 2015- Sep 2019

URL: https://dda.org.in/
Project Name: IDLI System

IDLI System is the major project of DDA. In IDLI system I developed

three Services -

- Mutation -> Changing of Ownership of DDA's properties.
- Conversion -> Lease hold Properties converted into free hold.
- EOT (Extension of Time)-> Application can apply here if any construction is pending on DDA's properties.

Softpro India Pvt. Ltd. Lucknow [Internship]

Jan 2015- July 2015

URL: https://www.polyprep.co.in

Major Project Topic - PolyPrep.
Team Size - 6
My Contribution - 100%
Technology Used - Asp.net

Minor Project

Topic - Online Library Management System
Team Size - 2
My Contribution -100%
Technology Used - Asp.Net

DECLARATION

I do hereby declare that the details furnished above are true and correct to the best of my knowledge and belief.

KAILASH CHANDRA JOSHI